♪〜
〜♪
（蒸気が噴き出す音）
（客Ａ）
ったく デミスラードのしぶきは
まだ 止まんねえのかよ
Damn! Haven't the Demislad
sprays stopped yet?
（客Ｂ）このまま
キャラバンごと立ち往生か…
We'll be stuck here with
this caravan forever!
（客Ｃ）飲んでりゃ
そのうち止まるさ 慌てんなよ
Have a drink and chill out.
They'll stop before you know it.
（ニコラス･Ｄ･ウルフウッド）
ぐぐぐぐっ
ニャー
むわあ…
（ギャンブラー）ギャハハハ
どうしたい？ もう終わりかい？
What's wrong?
You had it already?
Be quiet!
I'm trying to think!!
じゃかあしい！
今 考えてんねん
Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
（ギャンブラー）
あらそ　そりゃ失礼した
Nuts!
（ウルフウッド）
あかーん　状況は絶望的や
The situation is desperate.
Should I give him a head-butt
and make a break for it?!
このオッサンに頭突きかまして
トンズラこくか？
あっ あかん あかん
そないなことしたら あかんがな
No, no! I can't do that!
I keep forgetting
my profession.
自分の職業 忘れとるがなあ
She needs dancing lessons.
ヘタな踊りやなあ…
あっ 現実逃避してもあかん
どないする？ どないする？
I mustn't escape from reality!
What'll I do? What'll I do?!
What? You don't have pudding?!
（ミリィ･トンプソン）
ええ！ プリンないんですかあ？
（バーテン）
ほんのちょっと見渡しゃあ—
A simple look around will tell you
we don't serve that kind of stuff.
ここがどこだか分かるだろ
おねえちゃん
（ミリィ）プリン食べたいんです
意地悪しないでください
But I want to have pudding!
Please don't be mean to me!!
Are you listening?
人の話 聞けよ
Hey, what's the problem?
よお どないしたん？
Oh, Mr. Priest!
What a peasant surprise!
はあ！ 牧師さん
土偶ですね
“奇遇”や
"Pleasant."
しかし なんやなあ あんたらも
このキャラバンにおったんか？
What brings you here?
Are you guys in this caravan too?
That's right! Meryl and
Mr. Vash are here with me!
はい！ 先輩とヴァッシュさんも
一緒なんですよ
Y-You mean,
Vash the Stampede?
ヴァ…
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードか？
Yes. I'm surprised
you know him!
（ミリィ）そうです！
よくご存じですねえ
Know him, nothing!
He's The Humanoid Typhoon!
（ギヤンブラー）
ご存じもなにも あんた
ヒューマノイド･タイフーン…
GULP!
What's with the hand, buddy?
おう お兄ちゃん
この手なんだよ ええ？
I'm sorry, how careless of me!
おおお すまん すまん
不注意やったわ
Many pardons!
堪忍 堪忍
ナハハ アハハハ
No... I'm going insane.
あかん… 絶体絶命やんけ
ほお？ はっ
うわあ あかんがな
何すんねん
What are you doing, girl?!
The rest of my fare
is riding on this game!
この先の旅費をかけた
一世一代の勝負なんやで！
いいっ 参りました
I give up!
ひっ！ なんでやねん
What? Why?!
ホンマや
I'll be damned.
うふっ
（ミリィ）こんなに買ってくれて
ありがとうございます
Thank you for buying
all of these for me!
（ウルフウッド）ハハッ
礼を言うんは こっちや
I should be thanking you.
You saved my bacon!
ホンマ助かったで
ずっと大兄(おおにい)ちゃんの相手
してましたから
I'm pretty good at chess because
I always played it with my big brother.
チェスには自信があるんです
A brother, huh? Must be nice...
Got any other siblings?
兄弟かあ ええなあ
何人や？
There are 10 of us!
10人兄弟です！
You're the youngest,
aren't you?
はっ… あんた末っ子やろ？
That's amazing!
How could you tell?!
えっ すごい
どうして分かるんですか？
It's written all over you.
体全体で表現しとるがな
（ムーア）ハア ハア… あっ！
（ミリィ）あ？
（ウルフウッド）うん？
I'm sorry!
（ムーア）ご… ごめんなさい
Hey, aren't you
the dancing girl?
あっ あんた酒場で踊っとった…
ハッ　お願いです
かくまってください
Please, don't let
them find me!
Well, that was sudden.
…って いきなりやな
（ミリィ）うん
（ウルフウッド）ん？
Hey, buddy!
（男Ａ）おい 兄ちゃん！
A dancing girl just came through here!
Which way did she go?
ここに踊り子が来たはずだ
どっちに行った？
- Is she in trouble?
- Just answer the question!
なんか あったんか？
（男Ａ）いいから答えろ！
All right, all right.
（ウルフウッド）
分かった 分かった
You'll find her
hiding right behind me.
その子やったら後ろに
隠れとるで
あっ…
えっ！
なんだあ？
What?
I answered your question.
Now answer mine.
ちゃんと答えたったんや
こっちの質問にも答えたってえな
てめえには関係のねえ
ことなんだよ！
It's got nothin'
to do with you!
はあああっ！
（男Ａ）あん？
（ミリィ）キイッ！
W-What?
（男Ａ）な… なんだ？
How dare you waste food,
you ingrate!
食べ物を粗末にするなんて
この罰(ばち)当たり
あっ…
（発砲音）
（男たちのうめき声）
Treat food with respect, you!
（ミリィ）食べ物の恨みは
恐ろしいんですよ
落としたんは あんたやったやろ？
You're the one
who dropped them.
Um, thank you for your help.
I have to go now.
あの ありがとうございました
私はこれで
I heard gunfire
from over there!
（男Ｂ）
向こうから銃声が聞こえたぞ
Get everybody together!
We can't let her escape!!
（男Ｃ）仲間を集めろ！
（男Ｂ）逃がすわけにはいかねえ
Hey! Over here!!
（男Ｂ）おい こっちだ
（ムーア）はあっ…
（ミリィ）ウフッ
（ウルフウッド）あっ？
（ミリィ）ウフフフン
（おばさん）
おっきな おなかだねえ
６つ子でも産まれるんじゃない？
You're a big one, aren't you?
Are you expecting sextuplets?
エヘヘヘッ
Isn't it lovely out today, dear?
いい天気ですね あなた
Q-Quite, honey!
そ… そやな マイ ハニー
すみません ホントに…
I'm really sorry about this.
え… ええから
顔 出さんとき
It's all right.
Stay down.
- Did you see her?
- No, nowhere!
（男Ｂ）いたか？
（男Ｃ）いや ダメだ
She can't have gone far!
Find her, no matter what!
（男Ｂ）遠くへは行ってないはずだ
なんとしても捜し出せ！
（ウルフウッド）ああ なんで
こないなことになるんや
How did this happen?
This girl always
throws me off balance!
このおねえちゃんとおると
調子狂うで ホンマ
あっ…
It's bad for the baby, dear.
おなかの子に さわりますよ あなた
Oh, yeah!
Sorry about that, HONEY!
おお すまんな マイ ハニー
Good grief... It's been ages
since Milly went to do her shopping.
（メリル･ストライフ）まったく…
買い物に行くって出かけたっきり
戻ってきやしない
What on earth is
keeping that girl?
いったい 何やってるんですの
あの子は…
ハッ！
You're Vash the Stampede, aren't you?
（男Ｄ）あんた
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードだろ？
（ムーア）
ホントにご迷惑をおかけしました
I'm so sorry for
all the trouble.
We're just lending
a helping hand!
（ミリィ）
困ったときはお互いさまです
Since I'm in this deep already,
will you tell me what's going on?
（ウルフウッド）
ここまで関わったんや
わけぐらい教えてくれるか？
Actually, I'm...
（ムーア）実は私ここ…
（銃声）
（ムーアとミリィ）ひゃあっ
誰や！
Who did that?!
Get away from Moore!
（ジュリアス）ムーアから離れろ！
What?!
なんや…
Stop it, Julius!
やめて！ ジュリアス
They helped me!
この人たちは違うの
I'm sorry I'm late!
遅れてごめんなさい
You're not late, Moore!
そんなことないさ ムーア
Julius!
（ムーア）ジュリアス
Come again?
なんや… あれ
エヘヘヘッ
（蒸気が噴き出す音）
Julius and I have been
friends since childhood.
（ムーア）
私とジュリアスは幼なじみです
But he's the son of the owner
of the transportation company...
…と言ってもジュリアスは
デミスラード地方を行き来する—
輸送隊のオーナーの息子
...which passes through Demislad,
and I'm just a simple dancing girl.
私はしがない踊り子ですが…
So why are they after you?
なんで追われてんねん
It's Fondrique.
（ジュリアス）フォンデリックです
What? You mean Fondrique
as in the big city?
ええっ？ フォンデリックって
あの大きな街の？
Fondrique City's transportation needs
have been left solely to my caravan.
（オーナー）私のキャラバンは—
フォンデリックの街の輸送を
一手に任されています
Its abundant production plants
are guarded so tightly...
生産プラントが豊富な あの街は
警備が厳しく—
...that even I can't
get in without my pass.
手形がなければ
たとえ私でも入ることができません
So you're looking
for your pass?
（ヴァッシュ）
その手形を探してるのか
No, for my son...
いえ 私の息子です
本当の息子ではないのですが…
...although he
isn't my real son.
I'm actually the son
of the mayor of Fondrique.
僕は本当は
フォンデリック市長の息子
That's right.
I, myself, am the pass...
そう　キャラバンが
フォンデリックに入る手形は—
...which admits the caravan
into Fondrique.
僕自身なんです
（ミリィ）はあっ
So they're actually
after you, and not her?
やつらが追っかけとるんは
この子やのうて—
あんたっちゅうわけかい
That's still no
reason to run away.
けど 逃げる理由になってへんで
But we do have a reason!
（ムーア）理由はあります
あっ… んっ
I ran the day I discovered what
the person I thought was my father...
あの日 僕は知ってしまった
父だと思っていた人と
そして実の父が何をしていたのか
...and my real father
had been doing.
Yes, Fondrique did use
the caravan to import cargo...
確かにフォンデリックは—
キャラバンを通して
荷を輸入していたけど…
...but their cargo
wasn't all in boxes.
それは荷物だけじゃなかったんだ
Now, come here.
（男Ｅ）さあ こっちに来なさい
We bought you.
You have no choice.
（男Ｆ）
君の人権は我々が買い取った
選択することはできない
（少女）あっ… 放して！
お母さん お母さん！
Let go of me! Mother!
Mother!!
人をまるで物のように扱い
それで富を得ていたんです
They treat people like things.
That's how they got so rich.
That's horrible.
ひどい…
So, she's the new cargo?
それで今度の荷物は
この子っちゅうわけか
That's why we ran away...
だから僕たちは逃げだしたんです
...from all reality!
すべての現実から
Please do this for me.
（オーナー）どうか お願いします
I need Julius back!
ジュリアスを取り戻さなければ—
Without him, all trade will cease!
This caravan will go under!
交易で生計を立てている
このキャラバンは—
なくなってしまいます
$ $20,000,000.
2000万ダブドルだ
I won't do it for less.
それ以下では引き受けない
なっ！ 2000万
そんな大金…
20 million?!
That's ludicrous!
Then look elsewhere.
（ヴァッシュ）
ならほかを当たるんだな
むむっ… 分かりました
All right.
I'll pay your price.
お支払いしましょう
However, please let me include
one other condition.
ただし もう１つだけ
条件を加えさせてください
Thank you so much for
helping Moore to get out.
ムーアを連れてきてくれて
本当にありがとうございました
行こう
Let's go.
Where will you go?
どこへ行くつもりや？
Somewhere we can be free.
（ジュリアス）
僕たちが自由になれる場所へ
You're going through there?!
You'll be killed!
あそこを渡るつもりですか？
無茶ですよ
The caravan people know
every inch of this area.
キャラバンはこの辺りの土地を
知り尽くしています
They won't dare
follow us into there.
でも あそこを通っていけば…
Even if it means dooming
everyone in the caravan?
（ウルフウッド）
キャラバンの人たち
巻き込んでもか？
（ジュリアス）ああっ…
If you leave, they lose
their contract with the city...
（ウルフウッド）
あんたが消えたら—
街との契約がのうなって
キャラバンがなくなる
...the caravan goes under,
and everybody dies.
みんなで のたれ死にや
Any caravan that participates in
something like that should go under!
あんなことに協力している
キャラバンなんか—
なくなればいい！
I hope Fondrique goes under, too!
フォンデリックも
なくなればいいんだ
ハッ！
Don't give me that! People are
going to die because of you!
（ウルフウッド）
ふざけるんやない！
あんたらのせいで人が死ぬんや
Listen to me, kid! You can only
say that because you won't be there.
ええか？ ぼんぼん
あんたは逃げとるから
そない簡単に言えるんや
Say that after you watch them die.
目の前で人が死んでみい
言えるか？
Can you flee over
the bodies of the dead?
しかばね踏み越えて
逃げられるっちゅうんか？
We made up our minds to do this.
（ジュリアス）
僕たちが決めたことなんだ
あなたには関係ない！
It has nothing to do with you!
That's true...
確かに そうや
（３人）えっ？
Mr. Priest?!
牧師さん！
...however...
（ウルフウッド）けどなあ—
犠牲は少ないほうが ええ
...the fewer sacrificed, the better.
Am I right?
ちゃうか？
The fewer sacrificed, the better.
犠牲は少ないほうが ええ
Am I right?
ちゃうか？
Mr. Priest...
牧師さん…
Your freedom, or the lives
of the people in the caravan...
（ウルフウッド）
あんたらの自由と
キャラバンの人たちの命
どっちが重いか一目瞭然や
...it's obvious
which is more important.
I'll prepare you.
実践したる
あっ…
If you make a move,
someone will die.
あんたらが動いたら
人が１人死ぬ
Can you still move?
Can you still run?
それでも動けるか？
それでも逃げるか？
Show me how
determined you are.
あんたらの覚悟 見せてみい
Wait, I wouldn't do that...
ちょっとヤバいですよ それ
ホントにヤバいですってば！
...I'm not kidding!
（ウルフウッド）ヘッ
（空撃ちする音）
ハッ！
（ムーア）ひっ…
（ジュリアス）ハッ！
Thank you.
ありがとう
Don't thank me. You haven't
given me your answer yet...
礼なんか言うな
答えはまだ出てへんし
...and I think what
you're doing is wrong.
わいは あんたらの行為は
間違いやと思とる
We still thank you, sir.
それでも ありがとうございます
You're going with them?
行くんか？
How could I not?
ほうっておけないじゃないですか
If you're doing it
out of sympathy, don't.
同情やったら やめとけ
これ以上は
他人が踏み込んでええ問題やない
It's no longer
a problem for strangers.
But I have to do what
my big sister told me.
でも 中姉(ちゅうねえ)ちゃんに言われたんです
She said I should always
help people in need!
困ってる人がいたら
助けてあげなさいって
She does everything
I can't, so easily...
わいにできんこと
簡単にするんやなあ
It's really irritating.
むかつくでホンマ
Ow, ow, ow!
熱い 熱い 熱い
（ムーア）気をつけてください
Please be careful!
If it gets on you,
it will scald!
ヘタにかぶると
やけどじゃ済みませんから
Please go back!
（ジュリアス）もう帰ってください
There's no need for you to
put yourself in danger as well!
あなたがこんな危険なことに
つきあう必要はない
But, you know!
Anything can happen.
でも ほら
成り行きってあるじゃないですか
Besides, they say journeys
are emotional scars for life!
旅は巻き添え
ケガ一生って言いますし
しゃれになってませんよ それ
That's too true
to be funny.
（ミリィ）へっ？
（ジュリアス）フフフッ
おかしな人ですね　えっと…
You're really funny, miss, uh...
I'm Milly Thompson!
ミリィ･トンプソンです
（エンジンの始動音）
What did he ask you to do?
何を頼まれましたの？
Nothing nasty, I hope?
物騒なことじゃ
ありませんわよね？
Why won't you say something?!
何で黙ってるんですの？
うわあっ
（３人）ハア ハア ハア…
はあ はあ はあ
Look out!!
（ミリィ）危なーい！
（３人）ああーっ
Julius! Miss Milly!
（ムーア）
ジュリアス ミリィさん！
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか？
It was a little hot,
but I'm fine.
熱かったけど平気です
I feel so powerless!
なんて無力なんだ
Maybe he wasn't my real father,
but I loved him.
血はつながってなくても
僕は父さんが好きだった
That's why I
want him to stop!
だからやめてほしい
I don't want to build my happiness
on the suffering of others!
他人を不幸にしてまで
僕は幸せになりたくなんかない
But that's just nonsense...
でもナンセンスだよね
My actions are making
everyone suffer...
僕の行為が
みんなを不幸にしている
...including you.
ミリィさんまで巻き込んで
I think that priest was right.
あの牧師さんの
言うとおりかもしれない
But I'm fine.
私なら平気です
There they are!
（男Ｄ）いたぞーっ
（ミリィとジュリアス）あっ！
How long are you
going to stay silent?
いつまで黙ってるんですの？
なっ あなた いいかげんに…
Would you mind...
He wanted a kill.
（ヴァッシュ）殺しの依頼だ
えっ？ 殺し？
A kill?
That's right.
そうだ
And you accepted?!
（メリル）受けたんですの？
Yes.
ああ
Just as I thought,
you are a despicable outlaw.
やっぱり あなたは
卑劣な賞金首ですわ
Very well, I will now execute
risk prevention procedure.
なら私はリスク回避の業務を
遂行させていただきますわよ
Would you mind explaining
the entire situation?
最後まで事情を
話してもらえませんこと？
- After them!
- Don't let them get away!!
（男たち）追えーっ 逃がすなよ
うっ 背中が…
My back...
（男Ｃ）でやっ
（ミリィ）ああっ うっ
Julius!
（ムーア）ジュリアス！
Run! Run, Moore!
（ジュリアス）
逃げろ 逃げるんだ ムーア
I can't! I can't leave you!!
（ムーア）
できない そんなことできない！
キャーッ
Moore!
（ジュリアス）ムーア！
Julius!
（男Ｄ）坊ちゃん 逃げるなんて
もう考えないことです
You must stop running!
Is that my father's order?!
父さんの命令か
No, that is the order
of the entire caravan!
いいえ キャラバンの総意ですよ
（銃声）
Stop! Stop it!!
やめろ！ やめるんだ
I'll go back. I'll go back!
戻る 戻るよ
そ… そんなのダメ！
何のために ここまで来たんですか
But you can't!
You've come so far!
Milly's right!
（ムーア）
ミリィさんの言うとおりよ
あきらめないで ジュリアス
Don't give up, Julius!
（男Ｂ）さあ 行きましょう
Come on, let's go.
Julius...
ジュリアス…
（銃声）
（男Ｂ）うわあっ ぐわあ…
はあっ！
Mr. Priest!
牧師さん
むっ うう…
（男Ｃ）この野郎
You little...
どああーっ
ぐええっ
ぐわああ
ぐおおおっ
（ジュリアス）ムーア
Moore!
Jesus, what am I doing?!
まったく… 何しとんねん わいは
Thank you so much!
（ミリィ）ありがとうございます
でも なんで来てくれたんですか？
But what made you
decide to come?
I was infected
by your nosiness.
あんたの おせっかいが
うつってしもたわ
I think I actually
caught it from him...
（ウルフウッド）
あの男のかも しらんけど
So you mean business, do you?
そうかい 本気か
Then expect no mercy!
なら手加減せえへんで！
ん？
V...
ヴァ…
Vash the Stampede.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
You're kidding...
Did Dad hire him?!
まさか… 父さんが雇ったのか
Please, Mr. Vash!
頼みます ヴァッシュさん！
For the future of the caravan!!
（男Ｇ）キャラバンの未来のために
（ウルフウッド）うっ…
えっ！
（ジュリアスとムーア）ハッ！
Are you quite sane?!
正気か？ おのれ！
Yes. I swear to God.
ああ 神に誓って
（引き金を引く音）
ムーア！
Moore!!
（銃声）
だあああっ
はあっ！
ああっ…
（銃声）
（ムーア）ああっ
（ミリィ）いやあああっ
NO!!!
Y-You shotJulius!
ジュ… ジュリアス様まで
Our pass is dead!
手形が死んじまった
Hey! That wasn't part
of the agreement!!
おい 契約と違うじゃねーか
Your boss hired me
to stop them.
（ヴァッシュ）オーナーの依頼は
２人を止めることだ
He never mentioned
their safety.
生死については聞いてない
I've finished the job.
Leave the money and get lost.
依頼は遂行した
カネを置いて さっさとうせろ
What did you say?!
なんだと！
Don't do it!
Are you suicidal?!
（男Ｇ）やめろ！
命がいらないのか
（男Ｈ）
お… 俺たちが間違ってたんだ
We were horribly wrong! We should
never have gone to someone like him!
こいつに関わっちゃ
いけなかったんだ
He's just like they said!
He'll kill us as well!!
うわさどおりだ
俺たちまで殺されるぞ
ヒッ… ギヤアッ！
Now he's done it.
やってくれるで　うん？
Mr. Vash...
ヴァッシュさん どうして
どうして どうして！
...how could you?
How could you?
How could you?!
（殴る音）
How could you do
such a horrible thing?!
どうして こんなひどいこと
するんですかあっ
ミリィ
Milly.
Ma'am...
先輩…
Ma'am!
せんぱーい　ううっ
They're gone!
２人がいなくなっちゃった
あううっ…
２人が死んじゃったよお
They're both dead!!
You want to settle what
we started in May City?!
メイシティの決着
今 つけたろかい コラァ
That was a realistic performance.
迫真の演技やったな
Do you normally
kill with these?
こないな弾(たま)で
人 殺せるんかい？
（ヴァッシュ）なあっ！
（ウルフウッド）フンッ
（ヴァッシュ）ギャン
あー痛い 痛い 痛い
Ow...
Hey, don't fire those
so close! That stings!
それはこの距離じゃ
きついよ 君…
（ミリィ）ハッ
Thank goodness!
Thank goodness!!
よかったあ
よかったよお
I have a message from your father.
He says he's sorry for deceiving you...
（メリル）お父様からの伝言ですわ
だましていて悪かった
言い訳かもしれないが—
...and that it's no excuse, but he did
it all to protect you and the caravan.
すべては あなたとキャラバンを
守るためだったと
- I see.
- And one other thing...
（ジュリアス）そうですか
（メリル）それと もう１つ
あなたはもう自由だって
言ってたそうですわ
...he says you are now free to go.
Dad...
（ジュリアス）父さん…
（ムーア）ジュリアス
Julius.
Thank you.
ありがとうございました
Don't thank me,
thank him.
礼でしたら
あの人に言ってください
Hey, you forgot something!
忘れもんだ！
（メリル）
さあ 見つからないうちに
この車で
Now, quickly! Get away in
this jeep before they spot you!
From now on, we'll live
without relying on anyone.
これからは僕たちだけの力で
生きていきます
Except each other.
（ジュリアス）２人だけの力で
（ムーア）フフッ
Miss Milly, take c...
ミリィさん お元気で
フッ ウフッ
And thus, your name is being
spread across the planet.
（ウルフウッド）こうやって—
あんたの名前がこの星中に
とどろいて いくんやなあ
Maybe this is what
they call karma.
こういうの
因果っちゅうんかなあ
そうでもないさ
Oh, not really.
She's a good girl, isn't she?
（ウルフウッド）
あの子 ええ子やなあ
ホンマに ええ子や
She is so good.
（ヴァッシュ）そうだな
Yeah...
（ウルフウッド）
あんたも同じやけどな
You're just like her.
What? He really left?
ええーっ
本当に行っちゃったんですか？
All journeys come with meetings
and partings... and reunions.
旅に出会いと別れは
つきものですわ
それと再会も
That's true.
（ミリィ）そうですよね
I've got things to do,
so I'll be going now.
（ウルフウッド）
用事があるから もう行くわ
Will I see you again?
（ヴァッシュ）また会えるか？
（ウルフウッド）
ヘッ そら分からん
I don't know. And besides,
whenever I look at you...
それにな あんた見てると—
... I'm reminded of everything
I hate about myself.
自分のイヤなとこばっかり
目につきよる
It hurts.
つらなるねん
Nicholas D. Wolfwood...
ニコラス･Ｄ･ウルフウッド…
I'll be darned.
（ウルフウッド）まいったで
あんな答えもあるんか…
There was another
answer after all...
あんな答えも
... Vash the Stampede.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード…
♪〜
〜♪
（ヴァッシュ）
人には侵してはならない
聖域がある
All people have a sanctuary
which mustn't be touched.
A scar of sadness
which mustn't be entered.
踏み込んではならない
悲しみの傷痕がある
The living confront each other
to achieve their ideals.
その思いを遂げるために
生きている者どうしが相まみえる
In a quiet voice, the man
in the white coat told me...
白いコートを着た男は
静かに俺に言った
...that he had finally found me,
that he wanted my life.
“ついに見つけた”と
“お前の命が欲しい”と
That man smiled a smile
deeper than darkness.
その男は暗闇より深き
笑みを浮かべた
Legato Bluesummers,
a man fascinated by Death...
レガート･ブルーサマーズ
死に神に みいられた男
...only spoke quietly.
ただ静かに…